JOHN MICHAEL LACEDA

Brmerton, WA 98311

john.laceda@gmail.com 360.850.3086

PROFILE

Provide an excellent mix of professional development, technical expertise, operations and project management. Diversely experienced from start up to planning, turnaround, and growth - resolving systemic problems and creating solutions that improve operational efficiency. Excellent interpersonal and customer service skills. Able to quickly learn and adapt to new situations, configurations, and technologies.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux/UNIX, Mac OS X

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Objective-C, Ruby, C#, Visual Basic, Java, SQL

Databases: Microsoft SQL, MySQL

Network: Cisco IOS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Support Engineer

March 2015 - present

 $Comcast\ Technology\ Solutions\ (formerly\ the Platform\ for\ Media)$

Seattle, WA

Application Support Engineer

August 2012 - March 2015 the Platform for Media

Seattle, WA

- Troubleshoot customer issues with the Platform's service stack, digging through application logs if needed
- Teach Player Development Kit (PDK) technical training for new hires
- Subject matter expert of PDK within the support team
- Use network trace tools (i.e. Charles, WireShark)
- Create sample players for the customer
- Help with the support documentation of new product feature
- Escalate customer issues to product teams through JIRA as necessary
- Oversee and execute deploys of company products
- Frequent customer interaction of open/working issues until close

Web Applications Intern

June 2011 - August 2012

Kent School District

Kent. WA

- Developed Windows Gadgets and online mobile sites using JavaScript, jQuery Mobile, XML, and JSON
- Participated in planning, concept, testing, and implementation for internal applications in the ASP.NET platform and Microsoft SQL Server
- Collaborate with Technical Support Specialist team in configuration of an Apache Server on Debian for a MediaWiki site
- Developed internal applications in a team using Visual C# and Visual Basic on Microsoft Visual Studio and Microsoft Team Foundation Server
- Added functionality features and design templates to the district's SchoolWires site using JavaScript,

JOHN MICHAEL LACEDA

Brmerton, WA 98311

john.laceda@gmail.com 360.850.3086

HTML, and CSS

- Developed Photoshop scripts to utilize publishing media to the web
- Created custom workflows for Microsoft Sharepoint

Technical Support Specialist Intern

October 2009 - June 2011 Kent School District Kent, WA

- Provided excellent technical support to students and staff district-wide through phone, in-person, or remotely with Dameware
- Supported Windows desktop applications issues involving Microsoft Application Virtualization
 (App-V), Microsoft Windows XP and Windows 7, Microsoft Office 2007 and 2010, Forefont Anti-virus
 and other educational software
- Developed VBscripts to streamline issue intake for yearly refresh of all student laptops

CAD Operator & Production Team Lead

February 2006 - December 2008

Dimension4 Inc.

Bremerton, WA

- Led a team of production CAD Operators to complete work orders
- Trained and managed new hires to the team demonstrating procedures
- Managed files to provide a load balance for maximum IETM (Interactive Electronic Technical Manual) production output
- Successfully completed Joint Technical Data Integration (JTDI) work orders
- Produced electronic copies of scanned raster images of schematics using Autodesk AutoCAD
- IETM production added functionality to technical manuals through specialized application using XML and IntelliCAD

EDUCATION

Certificate in iOS & Mac Application Development

University of Washington Professional & Continuing Education, Seattle, WA Expected June 2014

Bachelor of Science Degree, Information Systems and Cybersecurity

ITT Technical Institute, Tukwila, WA Expected December 2014

Associate of Applied Science, Computer Network Systems

ITT Technical Institute, Tukwila, WA December 2009

Cisco Certified Network Associate Course Certificate of Completion

Olympic College, Bremerton, WA November 2007